(Amy:)If we're going to be staying
in this apartment,
(Amy:)would you be interested
in doing a little
(Amy:)redecorating?
(Sheldon:)Oh, actually, I would.
(Amy:)Great, what'd you have in mind?
(Sheldon:)Let's take every single thing
from the other apartment
(Sheldon:)and put it in here.
(Amy:)Well, how about we start
a little smaller?
(Amy:)Like moving
the furniture around.
(Sheldon:)You know, I have always thought
(Sheldon:)that this couch
would look fantastic
(Sheldon:)on the curb
in front of the building.
(Amy:)Look, we can't just
throw away Penny's stuff,
(Amy:)but we can ask
if she wants any of it back.
(Sheldon:)You know, I wonder how
she feels about
(Sheldon:)all this artwork.
(Amy:)Well, I'm sure
she misses this one.
(Amy:)I mean, it's the greatest gift
I've ever given anybody.
(Sheldon:)It truly does capture the beauty
of your friendship with Penny.
(Amy:)It may have appreciated
in value.
(Amy:)The artist killed himself
shortly after painting that.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, it seems only right
that she have it back.
(Amy:)I can't wait to see
the look on her face
(Amy:)when I give it to her again.
(Sheldon:)Look, it's the same smile
she has in the painting.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪